People pressed me to make some merch in response to Surrounded.
And so I listened.
OK, this first shirt that I designed got me in the middle.
It says Surrounded by Ignorance.
Now, I know it's me right there, but I know that y'all relate to this because this is where we be existing so much these days.
Surrounded by Ignorance.
And the face I'm making is what I know so many of you all are also making.
This shirt is available at Amanda Land Export.
It is available until August 22nd.
The next shirt.
I need you to get to the point.
OK, because I feel like we are just in this constant cycle of people just talking out their butt, out their neck.
It's so much pontificating that is going on.
You're just talking.
Please get to the point.
Last but not least.
Amanda over everybody.
Now, some might say, Amanda, this is a really self-centered shirt.
You're right.
Because you know what?
I've taken a lot of hits, particularly in the last two years.
I've taken a lot of hits, a lot of hits.
And I believe that I should be protected.
I believe that I should be preserved.
And those who came before us and publicly speak for us the way that I do did not get protected.
They were not preserved in the way that they should have been.
And now we uplift them as martyrs, but we don't change how we deal with the folks who are living like them.
Instead, we are continuing the practice of vilifying them, of expecting some incapable sense of perfection that is really just reflective of your own personal idealism.
And we're not really doing the work of really just trying to learn from them about the work that they're doing so that we can identify, well, man, if they're doing that, let me think about what I could be doing.
So, Amanda Over Everybody is my shirt that says, you rock with a real one.
And, you know, we don't flinch when people wear jerseys with a nickname on the back just because they could throw a ball through a hoop.
So, I don't think that you should flinch for wearing me on the front and saying, you know what?
I rock with my sis.
You can get all of these shirts at AmandaLandExports.com.